王储纳萨尔·本·哈米德·阿里·贾尼葬礼卡塔尔首都 多哈
- 这位是默罕默德·哈米德酋长 - 哈米德酋长
- This is Sheikh Muhammed Hamid. - Sheikh Hamid,
请节哀
I am so sorry for your loss.
大家字幕组
Euphrosyne 好乐嘚
翻译
EVERYONE
▆
大家字幕组
你们曾经一起致力于很重要的事业
You did such important work together
Noah  且水  凝夕
翻译
- 献身于... - 贩卖人口
- in the field of... - Human trafficking.
时间轴
梓梓  小鳄鱼
红小豆很逗
进出口贸易
import-export.
大家字幕组
特效
老王家隔壁
请允许我表达我的深切悼念
My sympathies.
- 好可怕 - 我的天
- Oh, scary. - Oh, my God.
校对
薛定谔也不知道
这里感觉像是六十度基地组织
It's like six degrees of Al-Qaeda in here.
压制
我真希望我们在这的时候 咱的无人机不会飞过来炸平这地方
I hope we don't drone this place while we're in it.
- 好吧 走这边 - 好的
- Okay, let's just go this way. - Yes.
\h  凝夕薛定谔也不知道
监制
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
那是奥马尔·艾尔·塞利赫上校
That's Colonel Omar Al-Saleh.
他是苏丹的军阀
He's a Sudanese warlord.
你可不能和他合影
You cannot have a photo with him.